simplydresses.com 2019-05-07

# Company Policies, Order Information, Payment Methods

## Return & Exchange policy

Please click here to see our full return policy. 

## Telephone Orders

For customers not wishing to place their order online you may email your phone number to [Support@Simplydresses.com.](mailto:support@Simplydresses.com) Please include an appropriate time to contact you and your time zone or state where you are calling from. One of our service representatives will contact you to take your order information within 24 hours. Or you can call us at our toll free number 1-855-373-7736 or our direct/international number 1-302-279-1072 between 8AM and 6PM EST on weekdays.

## Money Orders

Customers using money orders must fill out this form linked here and mail it with their money order. Before mailing the form, call us at 302-279-1072 for a final price quote and stock availability. Please mail all money orders to...

Simply Dresses  
105 Sleepy Hollow Dr. Suite C.  
Middletown, DE 19709

## Delivery Times

All orders of in stock merchandise placed before 9 AM EST will be shipped the same business day*. Orders placed after 9 AM EST will be shipped the following business day. 

* Business days are Monday through Friday (non holiday).

## Shipping

Please Note: **ALL SHIPPING PRICES ARE PER ITEM**

We ship most orders the same day they’re placed!

  * The selected item must be marked “IN STOCK READY TO SHIP”
  * Order must be placed on Business days (Monday-Friday, non holiday)
  * Place your order before 12 noon EST and choose Rush 1 Day shipping
  * Place your order before 9 AM EST and choose Standard 3-7 Days shipping

Other items will ship by the date listed with the specific item. The shipping date is processing day, not to be included in the shipping length of time.

## Low Price Guarantee

If you find a lower price on any dress we carry online, we will match it plus 2%. If you have already purchased a dress from SimplyDresses.com and find a lower price in the next 15 days of your order we will refund you the difference plus 2%.

**Exceptions:** Advertised price must be sold online at an _Authorized U.S. Retailer_! Product must be available for immediate shipment in size and color ordered. This does not apply to any dress marked sale, clearance, special auction, etc. Cannot be combined with any other discount, coupon or special offer.

## Payment Methods

We accept Visa, Mastercard, Discover, American Express, Money Order, AfterPay*, Paypal and Simply Dresses Store Credit. You can pay via checking account using Paypal**. To pay for your order with a money order do not place your order online. Mail your money order with your order information to...

Simply Dresses  
105 Sleepy Hollow Dr. Suite C.  
Middletown, DE 19709

Please include your name, phone number, email address, shipping address, style number, size and color.

*For more information about AfterPay, please click here.

**When paying by check (E-check) via PayPal please allow 6-8 business days for the E-check to clear. Once it clears your order will then be processed.

## Security

Our secure software (SSL) is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts your credit card number so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.

Simplydresses.com guarantees that your shopping experience will be safe. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges resulting from unauthorized use of your credit card. Simplydresses.com will cover that charge.

In the unlikely event of fraudulent use, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

## Privacy Policy

#### Safe and Secure Online Dress Shopping

This privacy policy governs the manner in which Occasion Brands, LLC (“us”, “we”, “our”) and our brands, which include but are not limited to, Simply Dresses and PromGirl, collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from you, a user (“User”) of the www.simplydresses.com website (the “Site”). This privacy policy applies to the websites, mobile websites, mobile applications and other webpages, products and services which we operate and in which we post a direct link to this policy. If indicated, it may apply to affiliated sites as well.

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their “Personally Identifiable Information” (“PII”) and “Non-Personally Identifiable Information” (“non-PII”) is being used online (collectively “Information”). Personally Identifiable Information, as described in U.S. privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that, without the aid of additional information, cannot be directly associated with a specific person. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally and Non-Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

This Site is hosted in the United States of America and use of the site is subject to U.S. state and federal law. If you are accessing our Site from other jurisdictions, please be advised that you are transferring your Information to us in the United States, and by using our Site, you consent to that transfer and use of your Information in accordance with this privacy policy. You also agree to abide by the applicable laws of applicable states and U.S. federal law concerning your use of the Site and your agreements with us. Any persons accessing our Site from any jurisdiction with laws or regulations governing the use of the Internet, including personal data collection, use and disclosure, different from those of the jurisdictions mentioned above may only use the Site in a manner lawful in that jurisdiction. If your use of the Site would be unlawful in your jurisdiction, do not use the Site.

**By using this Site, you are agreeing to the processing of your Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with this privacy policy.**

#### When do we collect Information?

We may collect Personally Identifiable Information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, use the website, enter a sweepstakes or contest, fill out a form, login with social network credentials, use live chat, open a support ticket, provide us with feedback on our products or services, follow or tag us on social media, or enter information on our site.

#### What Information do we collect from the people that visit our website?

You may be asked to provide, as appropriate, your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, payment information, date of birth or other details to improve your user experience. You may however, visit our site anonymously as registration is not required. We will collect Personally Identifiable Information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. You can always refuse to supply Personally Identifiable Information, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Site features or activities.

We may collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information about users whenever they interact with our site. This may include the user's geographic region, time of visit, browser type, IP address, operating system, the Internet Service Provider used, and other similar information. If you do not wish to share this information, please refrain from using the Site.

#### How do we use your Information?

We may use the PII and Non-PII information we collect from you in any or all of the following ways:   

  * To deliver the products and services that you have requested.
  * To process your transactions.
  * To manage your account and provide you with customer support.
  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better serve you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site feature.
  * To allow you to enroll and participate in a loyalty or customer relationship program.
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products.
  * To enforce our Terms of Use or other policies.
  * To inform you of updates.
  * To prevent, protect, detect, and mitigate against error, fraud, and other criminal activity.
  * As we believe necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, safety and security of our employees, customers and others.
  * As required or appropriate to comply with applicable laws or regulations.
  * To communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our affiliate companies or other third parties.
  * To do as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

#### Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. The Site uses cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf. We reserve the right to use cookies for purposes not listed here as needed in the future. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**If users disable cookies in their browsers:** If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.  

#### Do we share your Information with third-parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this Personally Identifiable Information confidential. We may also release Personally Identifiable Information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

However, Non-Personally Identifiable Information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We reserve the right to transfer or assign all Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information collected via the Site to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, liquidation, change in control, or other sale of all or a portion of our assets.

#### What about third-party links?

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### How does our site handle “Do Not Track” signals?

Please note that our Site does not support “Do Not Track” browser settings and does not currently participate in any “Do Not Track” frameworks that would allow us to respond to signals or other mechanisms from you regarding the collection of your Personally Identifiable Information or Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

#### Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

We may use third-party behavioral tracking vendors who use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past activity on the Website. The Information collected may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand your online activity.

#### Mobile Device Additional Terms

**Geo-Locations Informations:** Unless we have received your prior consent, we do not access or track any location-based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our mobile application or our services, except that it may be possible for company to determine from an IP address the geographical location of your point of connectivity, in which case we may gather and use such Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

**Push Notifications:** We may send you push notifications if you choose to receive them. If you wish to opt-out from receiving these types of communications you may turn them off in your device’s settings. 

**Mobile Analytics:** We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile software on your device. This software may record information, such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data and where the application was downloaded from.

#### Social Media

We may provide you the option to connect your account on the Site to your account on some social networking sites for the purpose of logging in, uploading information or enabling certain features on the Site. When logging in using your social network credentials, we may collect the Information you have made publically available on the social networking site, such as your name, profile picture, cover photo, username, gender, friends network, age, locale and any other information you have made public. By connecting your account on the Site to your account on any social networking site, you hereby consent to the continuous release of information posted on that account about you to us. Each social network may further allow you to set privacy controls around your information on its system, and our collection of information will always follow such controls and permissions. This feature is subject to continuous change and improvement by us and each social networking site involved, and therefore the available features and shared information are subject to change without notice to you.

We may use hyperlinks on the Site which will redirect you to a social network if you click on the respective link. However, when you click on a social plug-in, such as a Facebook’s “Like” or “Share” button, Twitter’s “Tweet” button or Pinterest’s “Pin” button, that particular social network’s plugin will be activated and your browser will directly connect to that provider’s servers. If you do use these buttons on the Site, the respective social network will possibly receive PII and non-PII, including your IP address, the browser version and screen resolution, and the operating system of the device you have used to access the Site. Settings regarding privacy protection can be found on the websites of these social networks and are not within our control.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared.

**According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:**  

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * We will include a link to this privacy policy on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * Our privacy policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
  * You will be notified of any privacy policy changes through an adjustment made on our privacy policy page.

**You can change or update your Personally Identifiable Information by:**  

  * Emailing us at support@simplydresses.com .
  * Calling us at (302) 279-1072.
  * Logging in to your account.
  * Chatting with us or by sending us a support ticket.

#### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to us. For that reason, we never collect or maintain Personally Identifiable Information at our Site from those who we know to be under the age of 13, and we do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

#### CAN-SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have commercial emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**  

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  * Send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our customers after the original transaction has occurred.

**To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM, we agree to the following:**  

  * Not to use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * To identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * To include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * We monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * We honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

**You may at any time unsubscribe from receiving future emails in the following ways:**  

  * Follow the instructions at the bottom of one of our emails and we will promptly remove you from our email list.
  * Log in to your account on the Site and update your email preferences.

We reserve the right to send you transactional or relationship based emails or notices even if you opt out of all voluntary emails. This includes information about your account, such as information regarding delivery of goods and services you have already agreed to and ordered, service announcements and administrative messages, information about warranty, recall, safety or security information, or notices about changes in terms or features of the Site.

#### Contacting Us

If you're not comfortable shopping online and would prefer to make your purchase via telephone, please give us a call at (302) 279-1072. Our customer service team will be happy to assist you.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, or the practices of this site, you may contact us using the information below:  
Occasion Brands, LLC  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
105 Sleepy Hollow Drive  
Middletown, Delaware 19709  
United States  
Email: support@simplydresses.com  
Phone: (302) 279-1072 

### Contacting Us

Occasion Brands, LLC has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time, so we encourage users to please check back periodically. When we do, we will update the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of this page. Each time you use the Site, the current version of this privacy policy will apply.

You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and read and absorb any changes.

#### Last Updated

**This privacy policy was last updated on 11/10/17.**
